Welcome to the
Manual Life Vietnam app! To request
cash withdrawal or dividend withdrawal,
please log in quickly to the
Manual Life Vietnam app using
facial recognition or fingerprint scanning.
Select "Cash Withdrawal or
Dividend Withdrawal" on a contract, then select the contract and follow the
instructions. In this step, enter the amount you
wish to withdraw or choose to withdraw the entire amount and select "
Continue". You can receive the money via
bank transfer or
cash at the bank. For bank
transfer, please check your
bank account information. Note: If you do not
have a bank account, please
register here. Then confirm the
information before clicking "Submit Request". If you
choose cash at the
bank, you need to enter the name and branch of the
bank where you will conduct the transaction,
then confirm the information before submitting the
request. At this time, you will receive an
OTB verification code via your chosen method, either
by phone or email. Enter the
OTB code to complete the verification process for
your cash withdrawal or dividend withdrawal request.  Your application has been
successfully submitted. Manif Life Vietnam will
notify you of the results within 2
to 3 working days.
Managing your insurance contract and using
online services has never been easier with Manif Life Vietnam. The
Manif Life Vietnam app is now
available on the App Store and Shopee. Are you
ready to experience it? Download the Manif
Life Vietnam app today to enjoy a
better life every day.